indulekha.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy

Indulekha.com ( Indulekha.com  or the Site ) respect your right to privacy. Indulekha does not spam or sell/lease its user information to third parties. This Privacy Policy covers Indulekha.com’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Indulekha. com collects when you are on the Site, and when you use Indulekha .com’s services. This policy also covers Indulekha.com’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that Indulekha .com’s business partners share with Indulekha. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Indulekha Biz does not own or control, or to people that Indulekha.com does not employ or manage. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

1\. The communication standards of the Internet industry transmit the URL of the site from which you visit Indulekha .com, the IP address of your computer, the IP address of your ISP, various attributes of your computer such as operating system, resolution and browser software, and the date and time of your various requests for pages on Indulekha .com. Indulekha file logging system automatically logs all of this information in its log files for its analysis. This information reflects our viewrship as a whole and is used to help us better understand and serve the users of Indulekha.com

2\. We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with Indulekha.com. You can browse some sections of the Site without any registration. However, certain activities like placing an order require registration. We may use this contact information to send you offers, info on new products and services based on your previous purchases.

3\. Visitors to Indulekha.com may also sign up with their name and email address for the free newsletter that Indulekha.com produces. Indulekha.com allows users to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us. To unsubscribe from the newsletter mailing list, send an email to support@indulekha.com with instructions. 

4\. Indulekha will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties unless it is to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. As an example, we send your information to a credit card processing company to process a payment you have made for the use of an Indulekha.com service. These third parties are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

5\. Indulekha.com may partner with other online services to offer a combined service. Whenever we offer such combined services, Indulekha.com will make it clear who the partner is and it will be entirely up to you to use or not to use the service. Where any personal information is passed along to the partner you will be informed prior to that sharing.

6\. Indulekha.com reserves the right to provide aggregate demographic information of its user base to advertisers and others so as to attract pertinent advertisers to advertise on Indulekha.com. We do not share personal information of individual users with advertisers.

7\. Information provided by you via general email inquiries to Indulekha such as your email address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties.

8\. Indulekha may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with Indulekha.com’s rights or property, Indulekha.com web site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

9\. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

10\. Indulekha.com places permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. Indulekha .com's cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

11\. Our Site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Indulekha.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

12\. Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to Indulekha .com. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Indulekha.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
